Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No living creature was harmed
during the filming.
Mother, you are wounded!
Who did this?
Wait, son.
I'm not wounded.
But, Cornelia...
he wounded her and escaped.
Go to the tent at once.
Come on, Bala!
What are you saying?
His face was covered.
I couldn't see.
They enter my mother's tent?
What are you doing here?
Find him!
My bey, I sent the alps.
They are searching everywhere.
We'll find him.
Are you alright?
That dog tried to kill me, son.
Mother.
Tell me all about it.
Mother Selcan!
Who are you?
Alps!
Alps! Help!
Mother!
What's happening?
He is running away!
Alps!
Catch him!
Hang on, my girl.
He stormed in and stormed out.
He knew the place.
It's apparent.
It's one of us, son.
Osman Bey.
Selcan Hatun is right.
That snake infiltrated the tribe.
Alps are searching.
He'll be found.
Many traitors stood behind us.
They looked into our eyes...
but we always waited for
the right time.
He'll be found.
Thank Allah.
Selcan Hatun is safe.
Let's leave her to rest.
If you allow us.
Thank Allah.
It's late, İbrahim Fakih.
Stay in the tribe tonight.
Do you allow it, my bey?
Slowly.
Cornelia.
How did it happen?
Where were you?
How did you notice it?
Mother Selcan was performing
prayer.
And I was laying there.
Someone entered.
Did you wound him?
No. I didn't have a sword
or a dagger.
I jumped him.
I couldn't think of anything
else.
We should go now.
Take some rest.
Thank you, Cornelia.
Good night.
Keep your eyes on her.
You weren't spotted, right?
No, my bey.
No one saw me.
The old woman couldn't
describe you either.
You hid yourself well.
Well done.
Thank you, my bey.
I did it easily.
They know that it's someone
from inside.
You will be cautious.
You are in a dark corridor, Osman.
You are blind.
Your suspicions are all cut
by me.
Selcan Hatun and Osman will
trust Cornelia.
My bey.
He ran away.
We closed the tribe.
We'll interrogate everyone.
We'll search the surrounding.
How can you let him go?
How can you?
My bey, I was chasing him.
He dissappeared.
Interrogate all the alps.
All of them!
The traitor is still
in the tribe.
Have you found anything.
We found this in my mother's
tent.
It belongs to Cornelia.
It seems like she hid the
poison there, my bey.
You were right, mother.
We blamed Zehra for nothing.
The snake was carrying the poison
on her neck.
What about today?
Have you learned anything?
But he is suspicious of you, Barkın.
He thinks the Mongols didn't kill Umur.
What does he have?
He can test me.
Because I ruined his power structure.
He looks for a weak spot.
Don't.
Don't, Barkın.
Don't underestimate him.
The one who underestimate his enemy
is destined to be destroyed.
What will we do?
Barkın Bey, may I enter?
Come in.
Barkın Bey.
İbrahim Fakih.
Osman Bey summons you.
What if he found us?
What will we do?
We'll clear all his suspicions.
She says that she didn't
have a weapon but...
she hides a dagger under
her pillow.
She didn't even touch
the dagger.
Wouldn't one run to their weapon
in such a state of fear?
Cornelia's treachery is obvious.
She poisoned herself.
Then, she made a new plan
after seeing my doubts.
She saved me from the enemy.
And became a hero, huh?
She couldn't do it all alone.
Mari's death.
Explosion at Söğüt.
Are they all related, my bey?
Not Cornelia.
She is a tool.
We need the one holding it.
But...
I'm suspicious of Barkın and Selvi.
They made a fait accompli with the
beyhood elections.
I thought of that.
What connection might they have
to Cornelia.
You'll figure it out, mother.
You'll make Cornelia speak.
My bey, allow me.
I'll make her speak.
If you scare the scorpion,
it'll poison itself.
We won't scare her.
As they killed Mari Hatun...
she will be punished.
An eye for an eye.
Don't worry, son.
For the pain she made Mari
suffer...
she'll pay severely.
Indeed.
Harmankaya Castle
You thought so long, Turgut Bey.
In the end, you are a man of the steppes.
What will you do with
the castle?
A castle is a cage for you.
But spoils? It isn't.
Gold.
It's good.
But not enough.
I'll enter your market...
and sell my goods.
But I won't give you a single coin.
Alright, you won't pay a single coin.
I'll pay you a tribute.
But the castle is mine.
It doesn't fit a bey to make a decision
without the council.
I want to hear what my alps
and beys want to say.
Osman is talking about conquest. I don't
want my alps to follow him.
You wouldn't want that.
Alright.
I rather wait than see Osman stronger.
Osman is already strong.
When he hears that you
took İnhisar...
he'll come at both of
your castles.
It won't happen.
If it does...
he'll face the consequences.
I think...
still, don't underestimate him, Nikola.
Don't underestimate him, Nikola.
We take gold as spoils.
Osman took hundreds of Fyling Flame
barrels from Geyhatu.
He has it all.
He didn't give us any.
If he comes at you with all of them,
it will be hell.
He doesn't have the Flying Flame anymore.
Without them...
Osman can't do anything.
And, how can you be so sure?
It's Osman, Kosses.
Is it possible to be sure?
But if he had the Flying Flame...
he would use it.
Right?
Anyway.
I have business.
Until next time.
Farewell.
Nikola is involved.
Dishonorable.
But this time...
he won't be saved.
Right?
Oh, Mari the Pretty.
She past away before seeing
her child because of her.
Wouldn't I rip her into pieces for
killing an innocent?
Cornelia hurt many, mother.
She was about to make brothers
kill brothers.
She hurt many poor people.
No punishment is enough.
An enemy faces you and draws
his weapon.
Snakes like her crawl into
you sneakily.
They don't deserve an honorable death.
Scorpions, centipedes...
but if I'm Selcan...
I'll dry her blood out!
May I enter, my bey.
Come in.
Do you know why I summoned you?
Beys have many mysteries, Osman Bey.
It's apparent that what you have
to say is important.
It's important.
Of course, it is.
The ones who attacked my mother...
and the ones who attacked my sheik
are the same people.
So are the ones who killed Umur Bey
and İhvaz Bey.
Their purpose...
is to demolish the mountains
I lay my back on.
I don't know the others.
But it was Mongols who killed
Umur Bey, my bey.
It's not the Mongols.
It's someone else.
I fought the Mongols.
Mongols killed Umur Bey.
Speak openly about what you
are suspicious of, Osman Bey.
Barkın Bey.
I've seen demons in disguise of
statesman, scholar, and warrior.
Many were good at hiding.
You can't make a decision over
suspicions.
The demon makes you know,
whatever he wants you to know.
Who is in your mind, Osman Bey?
Who are you suspicious of?
Nikola.
It's his style.
But...
we'll make sure.
We can't act as Geyhatu says.
I'll go to where Umur Bey passed away.
You won't doubt me now, Selcan.
I'll make you suffer one day.
Cornelia, my beautiful girl.
Mother Selcan.
Oh, my beautiful girl.
My brave girl.
You risked your life to
save mine.
Now, you are my daughter.
You are precious to me too,
Mother Selcan.
I made it for you with my
own hands.
To heal you.
to get you on your feet in no time.
To make you pay for the blood spilled.
It's so delicious!
Enjoy it, my beautiful girl.
Let it be a cure for you.
I'll see the corpses of the Mongol
warriors killed by Barkın and the field.
Whoever this enemy is,
in Mongol disguise...
but is something else.
Alright, my bey.
Let it be your way, then.
Tomorrow, the truth will be revealed.
We'll find out the truth.
You are allowed to leave.
May Allah help you, Osman Bey.
My bey, may I enter.
Come in.
News from Turgut Bey and
Kosses, my bey.
Whoever the enemy is, they say that
Nikola is with him.
Let them know, then.
They should release the bird
in the cage.
He should tell everything
to Nikola.
As you order, my bey.
İnhisar Castle
-Commander Antonio!
-I wouldn't let you stay here.
God bless you, Commander Niko.
The secret passage is open, sir.
If you want to take revenge, Osman and
the others will be at Kurt Strait.
Let's go, sir.
Get up.
He took the bait.
I knew it from the
beginning...
that dishonorable Nikola had a part
in Mari's death.
We knew it.
Now we are sure of it.
Now is the time to settle it.
Matheus will tell Nikola about
our location.
My only wish from God is...
to have that masked weasel,
who caused everything, be there.
They aren't brave enough to fight alone.
That dog will be there.
He should.
So that we can end it.
The gone won't come back.
I know it.
But the responsible will die today.
Kutay is coming.
Speak, Kutay.
My bey. They are coming.
It's time, Kosses.
We are moving!
İnegöl Castle
Argus, report!
The passages are closed, sir.
The walls are strengthened.
-We took cautions for entrances.
-Good!
Is this what you are strengthening the
castle with?
Good. Good.
I have only one wish.
İnegöl! This stone castle...
will be a stone grave for those
who wish to take it.
Don't worry, sir.
-What about the ditches?
-Ready, sir.
-Good.
-Sir!
Lord of İnhisar, Matheus is here.
Turgut took your castle.
And you came here.
Is that so?
I wonder why, Nikola!
You didn't come to the dinner that
you said you would.
Turgut didn't take my castle alone.
Turgut, Kosses, and Osman!
Osman?
Idiots!
Idiots... Idiot Kosses!
Idiot Turgut!
They wandered around...
and worked with Osman again!
They are loyal like dogs!
Then, Gündüz...
Gündüz didn't die...
Osman...
My soldier said that Osman
will be at Kurt Strait.
Let's finish it, Nikola.
I will, Matheus.
I will.
Mother Selcan.
I don't feel good.
I'm in great pain!
What is it, my girl?
What's wrong.
My stomach...
My stomach.
Allah Allah! Is it something
you ate?
Oh, oh...
I remembered Mari now.
She was in pain, just like you.
Oh, Cornelia?
Were you poisoned, my girl?
You drank sherbet.
So, this is where they attacked, Barkın?
We attacked, Osman Bey.
We attacked.
Umur Bey ordered us.
And we charged.
But it was an ambush.
True.
You were ambushed.
Alps. Boran. Cerkutay.
Check around.
See where they attacked from.
As you order, my bey.
Tell me, Barkın.
Where did the arrow come from?
Where did Umur Bey fall?
Where did they come from?
How did it happen?
We followed them this way.
But they lured us into a trap.
They first attacked here.
They charged at us from all
sides.
And we fought.
Brother.
My bey.
There are dry blood marks.
Alps.
Be cautious.
Söğüt
Selcan stopped me from seeing
Cornelia.
She just said that she is fine.
Something is happening in the tribe,
Ishak.
I need to talk to Cornelia.
Our companion will amuse him
for a while.
Osman wants to be our shadow.
But the darkness has no shadow.
We need to catch up with our
soldiers. There will be blood.
My girl. Let me tell you.
You must be poisoned.
Mari was suffering just like you.
Oh my!
You drank sherbet.
Yes. Surely!
There is a scorpion in
the tribe.
It keeps poisoning the innocent.
How couldn't I think that?
I don't understand it?
Why would anyone poison me, Mother Selcan?
You are right, my girl.
You are right.
Is there any other snake
than you to do that?
Yes.
You will look at me like this.
If you are a demon, I'm Selcan!
I wasn't born yesterday!
Look! That's how I poisoned you.
But my poison is nothing
like yours.
I'll make you regret everything!
My bey.
Arrow mark.
Is it a Mongol arrow?
Brother.
It isn't ours.
The lord has ours.
This is a Mongol arrow.
Have you found anything, Osman Bey?
Osman Bey.
Keep searching.
Alright, Osman Bey.
Barkın is aware.
Of what, sir?
That we aren't setting the
trap here.
Look, İshak.
Would you come to a suspicious
place...
with so little of an army?
Osman knew that we would
come here.
He knows that we'll attack him.
I'm sure that he has cavalry waiting
to destroy us.
Come on.
Soon, Turgut.
We'll be onto them.
Come on!
Give the signal!
What will we do, sir?
Great Darius.
I had doubts, now I'm sure.
Tell the archers.
We won't attack.
What do you mean?
İbrahim Fakih and Barkın won't
get revealed, Nikola.
We'll do it another way.
This is an ambush.
What does this mean?
Osman and the others took
my castle.
I'll destroy them.
What do you suggest doing?
My bey.
The Mongols set the ambush.
It's apparent.
It is.
The ones who attacked Barkın Bey
and killed Umur Bey are the Mongols.
We gave you a hard time, Barkın Bey.
But caution saves lives.
Give us your blessing.
It's yours, Osman Bey.
Now get your alps and head to Aksu.
We'll follow you.
Alright, my bey.
Alps, come on.
Konur.
Keep Barkın Bey followed.
He'll always be followed by
three alps.
As you order, my bey.
Boran.
My bey.
When Turgut Bey and Kosses comes,
we'll attack Nikola's caravan.
As you order, my bey.
The wolf won't return
empty-handed, Nikola.
Osman will hunt something.
Osman is waiting for me to kill him.
If we went there,
we would be the prey.
Sometimes, waiting is the only
way to hit.
These idiots were going to
outplay me.
The wind changed its direction.
Today is the end of them all.
Osman will attack that caravan.
Information is everything, Nikola.
We know him. He doesn't
know us.
Come on.
I didn't do it. Please!
Please, help me!
Stop, my girl. Stop.
I will help you.
Stop. Stop.
Look! This is your antidote.
If you tell me about your
treachery, I will give it to you.
I didn't do it.
Mari died.
She was my only friend.
I didn't kill her.
Zehra.
Zehra did it.
Zehra poisoned her.
Please!
I saved your life!
How can you do this to me?
Lying dog!
You old hag!
Even if you kill me, you won't
stop the rise of the darkness!
It will be your end!
You slandered my children!
You killed Mari and her child!
Weasel!
Poor Mari, her love for Turgut
blinded her.
She was about to become a Muslim.
I stopped her from her mistake.
It's good that she died.
What did you want from
a poor innocent baby?
What, huh?
A small Muslim Turk...
it's better to crush the head
of the snake when it's small.
Soon, Osman and you will share
the same fate.
You won't stop the darkness!
Enough! Enough!
Silence!
I will kill you!
You will tell me who is controlling you!
Never! Never!
You can never make me speak!
Aren't we supposed to lower the numbers?
It would be more desirable for
Osman.
No.
Nikola, Osman knows the importance
of this caravan.
If you lower the numbers, he'll know
that it's a trap.
So, he will attack?
They see themselves as wolves and
we as sheep.
But we are lions under that disguise.
Argus should lead the caravan.
You should hide.
When Osman attacks you,
I'll come from the rear.
Poor caravan masters will turn out
to be good swordmasters.
Osman will be stuck in between
and get smashed.
Great Darius.
It must be important news since
you hold it tight like that.
There is time, Nikola.
There is time.
Master Darius.
Master of Darkness.
To conquest a castle, you need
to break many things.
It's not only the walls that
protect the castle.
You should break the courage
of their commander.
The trust of his soldiers for him.
And the faith of his people in victory.
Now, this caravan will be like water for
İnegöl.
But it doesn't need a water.
İnegöl is a tree that needs to dry.
If that hidden face is working
with Nikola...
he might be around.
So, we'll be cautious.
-Barkın Bey.
-Speak, Cerkutay.
Barkın Bey.
Are your swords sharp?
If not, let me sharpen them.
My swords are always sharp.
Don't worry.
Good.
We'll take a position all around the road.
But we won't waste goods
We'll use them during our conquests.
Inshallah, the hidden face
will be there.
Inshallah he'll be there and we'll end
that snake who killed Mari.
Let's not forget Nikola, Turgut.
First, his caravan, then his castle,
then his head.
Aren't we late, Osman Bey?
Konur. Boran.
We'll attack from three sides.
But you'll go rear the caravan.
If they have a plan, you will
ruin it as wolves attacking sheep.
We'll do what's necessary.
May Allah bless our efforts.
Amin.
Alps! Come on.
Come here. Come.
Where are you going
without my approval?
These lands belong to Turks.
Give us the tribute, at least.
You are going to help Nikola, huh?
Osman Bey.
I think you need help.
Come here!
Nikola! Nikola!
It's our turn, Turgut.
Let's take this dog's
tooth out.
Let's do it.
Are you ready, Samuel?
Your sword will spill blood now.
Come on!
You snake!
So, you did all the treachery, huh?
You!
You've chosen the wrong side.
Alps, protect yourselves!
My bey!
You disgraceful weasel!
You are the head of the snake.
It's your end now!
Stay down!
Boran! Saltuk!
Catch him.
We are on it, my bey!
I won't allow this, Osman.
Boran!
Master.
Saltuk!
Boran!
I bear witness that there is no god but
Allah, and I bear witness that Muhammad
is the servant and Messenger of Allah.
Saltuk.
Master.
Osman!
You.
Verily we belong to Allah and verily
to Him do we return.
Amin.
Darkness won't leave its servants.
I'll save you, Cornelia.
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam, İbrahim Fakih.
Humans are strange, aren't they,
Kumral Abdal.
The poor girl you opened
your doors for...
the Christian child...
has risked her life
for her Muslim mother, huh?
It is. It's the heart.
Inshallah Allah will destine her
to be Muslim.
Inshallah. Inshallah.
You've spoken well.
How is her health?
It must be bad. We didn't see
her.
I didn't see the wound. They don't
let me in.
She is fine.
We would hear it otherwise.
Alright. Alright.
May Allah heal her, inshallah.
Inshallah.
They know Cornelia.
I can't leave her to them.
Even if you kill me, my master
will bring your end.
One of us dies and a thousand of
us born.
Did she speak, mother?
She has spoken the things
we already know.
But she didn't say who her
master is.
She won't die before Osman Bey
comes, right?
As she pleases. She doesn't
have much time.
If she speaks...
we might let her live.
I know that you won't let me live,
you old hag!
Enough!
Dishonorable.
Heartless.
How did you kill an innocent baby,
Mari who has seen you as a sister?
It was easy.
I sacrificed Mari for
our holy cause.
You all... You all believed me!
You killed Gündüz and Ayşe.
And Zehra too.
You are stupid!
Your master is the stupid one.
Both Güdüz Bey and Ayşe Hatun
are safe and sound.
Are you talking about me, Cornelia?
Osman Bey went to settle
some scores.
Our hearts are enlightened with
the light of faith.
We'll destroy your darkness.
You weasel!
You won't die before suffering!
Get ready, Cornelia.
This is the sound of the Gream Reaper.
Did Cornelia speak, mother?
She has.
It's just as we thought.
She was behind everything.
Cornelia is the traitor among us.
What are you saying, mother?
Cornelia?
Did Cornelia do this to Mari?
No.
It's not possible.
Mari and Cornelia were like
sisters!
It must be a mistake.
We'll find out, Kosses.
We'll find it all out.
But let's confirm this weasel first.
Demon! You will suffer!
Even if you kill me...
my master will finish you.
We killed your master.
No. No. You can't do that.
You aren't strong enough
to kill him.
We are.
It was easy.
Now, let's take you to your master.
Get up!
Your mouth.
Move!
No. You couldn't do that.
How did you kill him?
My master!
Stop crying!
You will speak in front of
everyone.
Did you kill Mari?
Why aren't you answering?
Did you kill my Mari?
Why don't you answer?
Speak, woman?
Did you kill her?
Speak!
I sacrificed Mari to the darkness
for our holy cause.
You traitor! She saw you
as a sister!
I will kill you!
Kosses!
Turgut Bey!
She isn't alone, Osman Bey.
Who is behind you?
Who made you do this?
Turgut Bey.
Was it him?
Speak!
Master.
My master.
You killed him.
Speak.
Did you do the Söğüt explosion?
My master died but the others
are still alive.
Your end...
will come from the darkness.
Take them.
O' people!
You all have seen it!
And heard it!
Turgut Bey's wife, Michael Kosses' sister
Mari, and her baby...
was her helper Cornelia.
My brother Gündüz Bey and Ayşe Hatun
were slandered.
They are innocent.
Cornelia and the spawn of darkness
that work with her...
tried to make us fight
each other...
and killed Mari in order to
do that.
Boran.
Come on.
Gündüz Bey!
Brother.
He is alive!
Osman Bey.
Gündüz Bey.
Ayşe Hatun.
Give me your blessing.
I was wrong.
I was wrong. Forgive me.
Forgive me.
It's yours, Turgut Bey.
It's yours.
And you...
trusted me without evidence.
Thank you.
My brother.
Forgive me.
You have our blessings, Turgut Bey.
Thank you.
Thank you too, Kosses.
Son.
Welcome.
Thank you, mother.
Mother.
Brother.
Those who killed İhvaz Bey and Umur Bey...
are the ones who attacked Söğüt.
Their intention...
is to make us fight each other.
But we didn't.
They wanted to stop the
conquests...
but we didn't stop.
İnhisar Castle...
belongs to Kayı now!
Long live Osman Bey!
We defeated the ones who wanted
to pull us into darkness.
Thank Allah.
The cause of Allah will spread
to the whole world...
if we step back...
may our swords be red with
our blood!
Allahu Akbar!
İnegöl Castle
Matheus. It's like you just
saw a ghost.
Do you know what this is?
It's a mark of war.
Only the brave men have it.
Not the idiots who flee from
their castles.
Won't you sit?
Matheus. Forgive my
curiosity.
How did you flee your castle?
A soldier.
A loyal soldier helped me escape.
A loyal soldier.
Loyal, huh?
Loyal? The loyal ones have died, Matheus!
The rest are the ones who surrendered.
Just like you!
Osman released you on purpose.
I lost many things today!
I lost my master who taught
me everything!
And you will lose something too!
You will too!
Master Darius?
You didn't lose me, Nikola.
But our cause is wounded.
Osman ruined our plans...
and took my most capable
student.
Thank Allah. We avenged my father
and uncle, Selvi.
We can sleep in peace now.
Thank Osman Bey, sister.
It's Nawruz time. Spring is here.
It's my first spring with Kayı.
Mashallah.
Orhan. My lion, are you a big brother?
He is a big brother!
Mashallah, ladies!
Evangel!
His teeth are like latches,
his way is Allah's way!
The evil people should stay
away from him!
The dreams of the tyrants
will be ruined.
My great Orhan!
He shall ride his horse,
his way shall be light.
He shall enter the water
but won't get wet.
His sharp weapon shall never
get rusted.
Oh, my great Orhan!
Mashallah, mother.
His teeth were visible. He must've
waited for you to grow them, mother.
Mashallah to my Orhan.
So, mother. We need to
dress Orhan now.
Wouldn't I, my girl?
He deserves all the clothes!
Come here.
Mother, why did you rip it off?
It's the customs, Aygül.
It's for his teeth to grow easily.
Yes, ladies. We should help him.
We've overcome all the traps
they set before us.
We defeated the dogs
of the devil.
It's all because of your
trust for me.
Thank you.
Thank you, my bey.
Now, our way and friends
are apparent.
Geyve.
Nekece. Aksu.
Lefke.
And Gemlik.
Inshallah...
we'll raise the flag of Kayı there.
As we talked about before, we sent
the scouts.
We won't let a single caravan go to
İnegöl now.
And I informed all the lords.
Whoever trades with İnegöl...
will face our sanctions.
We surrounded them, Osman Bey.
We'll go to the oppressed
with the sword of justice.
We'll stop their suffering.
We'll kill the tyrants.
But firstly...
the head of the tyrants,
Nikola.
You aren't dead.
The mask?
It was someone else!
It was a game?
And you didn't tell me.
I didn't.
I couldn't, Nikola.
For our cause.
I'm so sorry for what you lost,
Master Darius.
Osman took something from all of us.
Yes, Osman wounded us severely.
But we also took something
important from him.
His suspicion.
He thinks that he destroyed us.
I won't stop, master.
I'll destroy him.
I'll destroy all his dreams...
his goals.
I will destroy him.
-When the time comes, Nikola.
-The time!
I choose the time now, master!
I...
won't wait!
I won't stop!
Whatever is in my castle!
Diamond, ruby, gold, precious metals!
I will sell whatever I have!
All of it!
I will gather everyone from everywhere!
I will get everyone here!
Whoever sells his sword!
All of them!
I have only one goal now!
It is not reviving!
I will bury the Turks where Rome lays!
Nikola!
The war here is stopping.
Emperor Andronikos and Sultan Mesud will
sign a peace treaty.
No! No! No!
Master Arius, do you think I, Nikola...
...would listen to that stupid emperor or
poor Sultan?
Osman will die!
He will die in my hands!
From now on, we will sharpen our swords
for Inegöl Castle.
All of them will be sharpened to kill the
infidels in İnegöl Castle.
I, son of Ertugrul Gazi, Osman Bey...
...swords will not be lowered until
Inegol is conquered, I order!
Inegöl's walls will not be able to stop
us!
-Can I come in, my Bey?
-Come in!
There is news from Sultan Mesud, my Bey.
Sultan Mesud...
...is waiting for me in the tavern.
Saltuk too drank the martyrdom sherbet,
brothers.
We lost many brothers, Boran.
We lost many brothers.
We didn't lose them.
We bid farewell to them.
Right, we bid farewell to them.
To that holy place.
To heaven.
I hope, brother.
Thankfully, Saltuk's revenge was taken.
But still my heart aches, brothers.
No one can fill his place...
...their places.
Cerkutay, I am hungry!
Who is here!
My valiant Kayı is here!
Are you hungry?
Whenever I am hungry...
...I find myself here as well.
Cerkutay always finds something to eat.
Let's eat! Come on.
Come on.
-Ayran.
-Yes it is.
First, say ''Bismillah''.
-Bismillah.
-Well done! Open your mouth.
Horses are coming, they are coming,
coming! Hop! Well done, my valiant!
Eat fast, go fast.
Cerkutay...
...we lost Saltuk but...
...Kayı is our comrade now.
He is.
He is! My valiant Kayı!
Praise be!
-Father.
-What did you say?
Father.
Did you say ''father''?
He said ''father''!
-Father.
-Father!
-As long as you call me father...
...I will call you...
...Kayı Saltuk.
Kayı Saltuk Alp.
May you be brave as my brother
Saltuk...
...and trustworthy as my brother
Saltuk.
Söğüt
Oh, people!
It is a happy day for the people of Söğüt!
The protector of the Anatolian land...
...the sharp sword of Islam
...the greatest Sultan ever,
Mighty Sultan Mesud is coming to Söğüt!
We will destroy all that is ingrained
in them!
Wake up!
You are the first ones awake!
You woke up to destroy!
Not only Sultan Mesud!
The great commander of the Greek
lands...
...Emperor Andronikos is also coming to
Söğüt!
I don't understand.
-What?
-Why?
The negotiation in the tavern will
conclude Osman Bey's decision.
His Highness, Sultan Mesud.
He is coming!
Welcome, my Sultan!
-Welcome, my Sultan!
Welcome, my Sultan! We are so glad to
see you, my Sultan.
Welcome, my Sultan!
Hold everywhere.
Close the entrances and exits until
the Sultan leaves.
Aghas, no one can enter.
We are the people of Söğüt.
Also, Osman Bey knows us.
-Let us in.
-Don't wait here.
-Who is that?
-I hope this is good news.
The Emperor.
I hope this is good news.
What kind of pain is this, mother?
It comes and goes.
Toothache is hard, my girl.
I will prepare some medicine for you.
You have to wait a while.
Bt you will get better, I hope.
The Emperor is in Söğüt, mother.
This makes me worry.
I hope it is good news.
Since both Emperor and Sultan Mesud came
to my Osman's feet...
...I am sure it is good news.
I hope, mother.
They played many games but we destroyed
them all with Allah's help, thankfully.
Thankfully, we did.
We did it with the strength Allah gave us.
May it always be.
Come on, drink this.
May it be healing.
In the name of Allah.
Welcome, Osman Bey!
-Welcome, Osman Bey!
Stay cautious. We may be surprised.
Welcome, Osman Bey!
Your sword, Osman Bey.
I know about what happened, Nikola.
But know that no anger, no revenge will
prevent this peace.
Of course, my Beloved Emperor.
I lost all my power but...
...Rome! May Rome always live!
Nikola, your personal anger is gone
the minute you sit at this table.
We will expand the union agreement
we signed with Geyhatu...
...and sign it with Sultan Mesud as well.
Aya Nikola...
...I once accepted your testimony.
Once, sent an army upon you.
But today is about peace.
Neither you nor Osman can't prevent this.
Honorable Sultan...
...everything you say will happen, today.
But tomorrow...
Your Highness, Sultan Mesud.
Emperor Andronikos.
...everywhere will be covered in blood.
Nikola!
Osman Bey!
We must inform Master Arius.
Go find him and inform him.
Tell him we are ready to kill everyone in
the tavern if the Master orders.
Osman Bey...
...the treaty you signed with the Lords
and Emperor Andronikos will be extended.
The State of Seljuk will be a part of this
treaty.
Of course, with new conditions and
additions.
Geyhatu is prisoned by Argun Khan.
Nökers are not under one roof.
They come in parts.
Thus, they are not dangerous.
I won't back off from my fight and my
conquest.
Osman Bey, you took İnhisar.
You killed the Lord of Inhisar, Mateus.
All these are enough reasons for me to
send you an army.
Andronikos is right.
You took advantage of Geyhatu's absence
and attacked immediately, Osman Bey.
A Bey's responsibility is to protect
his lands first...
...then attack.
We had a common enemy so we
made a deal.
But there is no deal from now on.
Two countries are here looking for a way
for peace, Osman Bey!
You can't act on your own.
We want this for the safety f the people.
Am I defeated so that I have to make a
deal I don't want to!
We are forgiving what you had done,
Osman Bey.
I've done nothing to be forgiven.
To no one.
But...
...since you want peace...
...in that case, I want Aksu's and
Karaçapuş's taxes.
And I would like to graze my animals
in the pastures around it.
I want the Turkmens who want to come
to far away tribes and see prosperity...
...to be led the way.
I want everyone who says they are
going to Osman Bey to be allowed.
I want them to be given horses, swords.
For Nikola...
...I have the mines he has from now on.
I said my conditions.
You've heard.
If there are two countries at this table
...
...then we must negotiate.
Tell me, I am listening.
It is really hard to convince the Lords
of these conditions.
But I accept.
Clerk.
Nikola!
Osman Bey.
You got what you wanted again, right?
But your soul is still inside your body,
Nikola.
I don't give a damn about the treaty these
two old men made.
Do you know that I will kill you, right?
With my own hands.
If you dare to break this treaty...
...I will be waiting.
Then, I will kill you with my sword.
You see how calm I am, don't you?
This is the calm before the storm.
Nikola!
We had to do this.
A leader can have no other purpose than
to keep the state standing.
Don't worry Sultan Mesud.
We didn't make a mistake.
This peace will reign in this land
for decades.
That's enough time to breathe
a sigh of relief.
Making peace is easy, Emperor.
The hard thing is to make it permanent.
I am sure you will do your part
in this matter.
I want to trust you as well, Sultan Mesud.
To a lasting peace, Emperor.
My Orhan!
Malhun...
...did you distribute my Orhan's boiled
wheat to the whole tribe?
The Hatuns did it, mother.
Zehra, bring the tray. Come on.
What did you choose, my lion son?
Your mother couldn't see what you
chose.
Your mother doesn't know.
She didn't see, this poor woman.
Hatuns!
My Kayı chose an Akça(money).
-Did you?
-My valiant will be an honest merchant!
Will you be a merchant, my lion son?
Stand up. Come on, my girl.
In the name of Allah!
May you be a good son to your mother
and your father!
-Amen!
Let your pockets overflow like these
wheat.
Amen!
May your heart and life be blessed
like this!
May your worst be strong.
May Allah increase your knowledge!
May your sword always be sharp
against the oppressors.
-Amen!
In the name of Allah!
My Valiant!
Let's see which one my valiant chooses.
Come on, our valiant!
What will you choose?
Praise be!
-Praise be to my lion!
-Praise be!
Praise be! Mother...
...Aktemur chose an inkstand, remember?
Right!
Let's see what Alaaddin will choose.
I hope he chooses what's best, mother.
My son will be a warrior!
He will follow in the footsteps of
his mother and father.
I hope so.
Come on.
His Bala Mother, I want you to pray for
my Orhan.
Of course!
Mother.
Come here, my Orhan.
In the name of Allah!
Praise be!
May your black mountains never fall.
May your big tree with a shadow don't
get cut down.
May your clean water flowing
like blood doesn't dry up.
May your wings don't get broken.
Amen.
May Almighty Allah not make you needy.
May your horse run like the wind.
May your sword never get down.
May you not be harmed while you fight.
May your hope always last.
Finally...
... may you never lose your faith.
-We made your prayer, may it be accepted.
-Amen!
May Almighty Allah...
...forgive all our sins, in the name of
Muhammad.
Amen!
May those who say ''Amen!'' to this prayer
see Allah.
Amen!
Darkness takes all disguises...
...Nikola.
Because it is everywhere.
What is this preparation for, Sir?
I received a letter from the pope.
Argun wants to unite with the papacy...
...and take Jerusalem from the Muslims.
I am going to Jerusalem.
Nikola...
...you will fight.
For our cause.
You will attack Osman with cruelty
he has never seen before.
I've always fought.
Still do.
You weren't here.
Now you are leaving.
For Jerusalem, Nikola.
I trusted you.
What will I do now?
I made you the bey of two tribes, Barkın.
You grew stronger.
Use this power wisely.
If I see even a faint light when I return
...
...I will bury it in my darkness.
You will...
...sleep, Barkın.
You will be with Osman until it is time.
You will be his friend for our cause.
I signed the peace treaty they wanted.
Did you make peace, Osman Bey?
With Nikola?
Sultan Mesud and Emperor were together.
Should've I said no, Turgut Bey?
But...
...I got everything I wanted.
Don't, Osman Bey!
Don't!
You can't have given up on conquering
İnegöl, can you?
I made the deal.
But you won't stop.
We will corner İnegöl so bad that...
...Nikola won't be able to even breathe.
That's better!
Thank you, Osman Bey!
Nikola was already my archenemy.
I'm gonna hit him for my friend
one more time.
It's my honor.
We must put Nikola in such a position
that...
...he gets slap after slap, Kosses!
Even his people will prefer Kayı to him.
Thus...
...if they don't give me Nikola's mines...
...I said I wouldn't accept the treaty.
Thank you!
Without the mines, Nikola's income
will fall in half.
It will.
From now on, the mines are property of
Kayı.
Thank you.
Let him become very weak...
... so that when his people
turn their backs on him...
...he will lose all his strength
and weapons.
First I cut his connection to İnegöl.
Now...
..I'm going to cut his carotid.
Byzantine's brave sons!
We have no longer have anything to do with
the coward emperor or the vile lords!
What will we do now?
We will ride our horses both to east and
west!
We will gather all the mercenaries here!
All of them!
You will bring me Peteleks, Kumans,
Baltalı Barbar Vareks.
You will bring the Kumans who will cause
Osman to extinct to me!
Clear?
Clear, Sir!
-Clear?
-Clear, Sir!
Good!
I will...
...destroy you, Osman.
I will destroy you!
I will cut his head...
...off his body and...
...throw it to the Pope's feet!
I will say, ''Here!''...
...''Osman Bey is here''
Since the emperor and the lords left me
alone in this war...
...I will say that I won this war
on my own!
On my own!
No Caesar!
I will say that I became Caesar!
I did!
Aya Nikola!
I will only open one grave for your
seven lineages!
I will bury women, children, and
old people in a single grave!
I swear! I swear!
I will carry...
...Kosses' head from castle to castle!
I will carry that Turgut's head, who
trusts himself too much...
...from tribe to tribe!
I swear on Caesar that...
...I, Aya Nikola...
...will be called for ages!
Those who wrong Nikola...
...always pay the price.
All of you will pay!
All of you!
Forgiveness and great reward.
What a beautiful truth Allah
the zealous told.
My Almighty Allah.
For the sake of our Prophet Muhammad...
...in honor of the most honorable
book you sent him...
...may you make my feet firm
on the cause of Islam.
My Allah...
...I swear by the night, the day, the
throne and your ninety-nine names that...
Give victory to my sword for
the cause of Islam...
...which I raised for the cause of Islam.
The Prophet Ekrem was patient with
infidels in the Hudaybi Agreement.
His patience opened the doors of Mecca
to our Prophet and his people.
Those infidels thought our Prophet
would stop.
But the great Prophet...
...got even stronger.
Oh, the one who is generous...
...my merciful Allah...
...you are the Rabb of those who stay
patient for theşr cause.
Until I am granted the conquest of
İnegöl...
...make time my friend, my Rabb.
My Allah...
...keep me on your way.
My Allah, I have no other purpose than to
spread the light of Islam to the world.
To wave the banner of Islam all over the
world, choose me ane my lineage, my Allah.
Amen!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com